{
    "id": "285b40ec923e4a75a8f286817d9a4f07",
    "title": "Interrogative pronouns exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "359d8b1a43c547d8873b6ee04afd7071",
            "title": "Interrogative Pronouns Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "———————— did you do then?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "What",
                        "Which",
                        "How"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "———————— would you like to eat?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "What",
                        "Which",
                        "Who"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "———————- is knocking at the door?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "What",
                        "Which",
                        "Who"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "———————- is your phone number?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "What",
                        "Which",
                        "Who"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "———————– do you want to see?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "What",
                        "Who",
                        "Whom",
                        "All of the above"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                },
                {
                    "question": "————————- will he say?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "What",
                        "How",
                        "Who"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "———————– did you see?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "What",
                        "Who",
                        "Whom"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "About ———————– are you speaking?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "who",
                        "whom",
                        "what",
                        "All of the above"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                },
                {
                    "question": "———————– came here in the morning?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Who",
                        "Whom",
                        "What"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "By ———————– was this book written?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "who",
                        "whom",
                        "what"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "———————- do you mean?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "What",
                        "Why",
                        "How"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "———————— do you think took the money?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Who",
                        "Whom",
                        "Why"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "———————– is better – wisdom or riches?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Which",
                        "What",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "——————– do you think is right?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Who",
                        "Whom",
                        "What"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "———————— is a continent?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Which",
                        "What",
                        "Why"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}